thank you
[Music]
when most kids are busy watching
stranger things or playing RoboCop our
kids here have been busy building robots
and representing India at none other
than a global World platform
[Music]
great pleasure to welcome the Innovation
story team five amazing kids who are
representing India the first Global
challenge or fgc what makes these kids
special and their achievement even more
incredible of rising above circumstances
of staying hungry of dreaming big and
making them come true through sheer grit
passion enthusiasm and meneth these are
kids who come from very modest
backgrounds their parents are daily wage
owners it's not just the fact that
they're representing India at a global
platform in fact it reminds me of a
Hindi kahawat
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
people achieve their true potential but
what was really inspiring was the
passion that you can see in in what
they're doing when I read about what
they've achieved and today we heard what
they've achieved it was just from the
bill it was a goosebump feeling I mean
this is something we felt that you know
amazing achievement of this outstanding
you know bunch of kids and we felt that
as I said you know what we had to
support you we are really proud of what
you know you guys are doing
[Music]